>> Are you ready, kids?
>> 孩子们，准备好了吗？
All: Aye, aye, Captain!
全体：是啊是啊，队长！
>> I can't hear you.
>> 我听不到你说话。
All: Aye, aye, Captain!
全体：是啊是啊，队长！
>> ♪ Ohh... ♪
>> ♪ 哦... ♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
>> ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
>> ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
>> ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
>> ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：海绵宝宝！
>> ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
>> ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
All: SpongeBob SquarePants!
>> Ready?
全部：海绵宝宝！
>> 准备好了吗？
All: SpongeBob square pants!
全部：海绵宝宝方裤！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
海绵宝宝！
>> SpongeBob
>> 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
♪ ♪
>> Ungh!
>> 呃！
Okay, SpongeBob, it's your turn.
I'm ready!
好吧，海绵宝宝，轮到你了。
我准备好了！
>> Okay, Patrick, here I come.
>> 好吧，帕特里克，我来了。
Whoa!
哇！
>> Nice landing.
>> 着陆顺利。
Darn. I missed.
该死。我错过了。
SpongeBob,
look out for my body!
海绵宝宝，
照顾好我的身体！
Ugh!
啊!
Oof.
>> Ahh!
钱币。
>> 啊！
Patrick, maybe we should play
帕特里克，也许我们应该玩
something that involves
less thinking.
涉及到的东西
少思考。
>> Okay.
>> 好的。
>> Hey, maybe we can play a game
>> 嘿，也许我们可以玩个游戏
with this ball
that was buried under here.
用这个球
就埋在这儿了。
>> Ball!
Let me see it.
>> 球！
让我看看。
What a weird ball.
多么奇怪的球啊。
>> Well, who knows how long
it's--Ahh!
>> 好吧，谁知道要多久
这是——啊！
Mother of Neptune!
海王星之母！
Get it away from me!
把它从我身边拿开！
>> There's nothing to be
afraid of, SpongeBob.
>> 没有什么可做的
害怕，海绵宝宝。
It's just a little worm.
这只是一条小虫子。
See?
看？
>> You're right, Patrick.
>> 你是对的，帕特里克。
I'm sorry we destroyed
your nest, little worm.
很抱歉我们毁了
你的巢，小虫子。
I promise it won't happen again.
我保证这种事不会再发生了。
Look, Patrick.
看，帕特里克。
>> Looks like he's taken
a fancy to you.
>> 看起来他已经被带走了
对你有好感。
>> Yeah.
Hey!
>> 是的。
嘿！
Why don't we invite Mr. Wormsley
to stay at my place,
我们为什么不邀请沃姆斯利先生呢
留在我的地方，
at least until his nest
grows back?
至少直到他的巢
又长回来了？
>> That sounds delightful.
>> 听起来很令人愉快。
>> Gary.
>> 加里.
Gary, wake up.
加里，醒醒。
That's right.
Just bring him in here.
这是正确的。
只要把他带到这里来就可以了。
Careful. Careful, now.
That's right.
小心。小心点，现在。
这是正确的。
>> Meow.
>> Oh, hi, Gary.
>> 喵。
>> 哦，嗨，加里。
Are you ready to meet
your new friend?
你准备好见面了吗
你的新朋友？
>> Meow?
>> That's right.
>> 喵？
>> 没错。
Say hello to Mr. Wormsley.
向沃姆斯利先生问好。
>>
>>
>> Something tells me
they don't like each other.
>> 有件事告诉我
他们不喜欢对方。
>> Come on, now.
Guys, come on.
>> 来吧，现在。
伙计们，来吧。
Let's touch soft parts
in a friendly manner.
让我们触摸柔软的部分
以友好的方式。
You're just saying hi.
你只是打个招呼。
That's it.
There you go.
就是这样。
就这样吧。
That's it.
就是这样。
Oh, I knew you could get along.
哦，我就知道你们可以相处得很好。
There, there, there you go.
See? Friends.
那里，那里，就在那里。
看？朋友们。
>>
>> Ow!
>>
>> 噢！
Oh, my goodness!
哦，我的天啊！
Patrick!
Ow, ow!
帕特里克！
噢，噢！
Patrick, please, do something!
帕特里克，求求你，做点什么吧！
>> Uh, SpongeBob,
I got to get going.
>> 呃，海绵宝宝，
我得走了。
I'll check in on you later
我稍后会查看您的情况
and see how your new pet
is doing, okay?
看看你的新宠物怎么样
正在做，好吗？
>> Okay, Patrick.
See you later.
>> 好的，帕特里克。
稍后见。
Oh!
Get it off me!
哦！
把它从我身上拿开！
Somebody, please!
Please!
有人请吧！
请！
Click!
点击！
All right, Gary,
好吧，加里，
just so there isn't
any more upset,
只是这样就没有
再心烦意乱的话
I'm going to ask that you sleep
on the guest newspaper tonight.
我要问你睡觉
今晚的客报上。
And Mr. Wormsley is going to be
sleeping in here with me.
沃姆斯利先生将会
和我一起睡在这里。
>>
>>
>> Now, now, Gary.
There's no need for protest.
>> 现在，现在，加里。
没有必要抗议。
See? I fixed it up
all nice for you.
看？我修好了
对你来说一切都很好。
There you are.
你就在那里。
Night, Gar.
晚上，加尔。
>>
>>
>> Ugh.
>> 呃。
Sounds like Patrick is having
one of his night fits again.
听起来帕特里克正在经历
他的某个夜晚又合适了。
I'll just close the window.
我就关上窗户吧。
>>
>>
>> Mr. Wormsley!
>> 沃姆斯利先生！
>>
>>
>> Whoa!
>> 哇！
i-I-I'll be back,
Mr. Wormsley.
我-我-我会回来的，
沃姆斯利先生。
I'm gonna go get help.
我要去寻求帮助。
Whatever's wrong with you,
don't move.
不管你有什么问题，
别动。
Just, uh, read the sports
section or something.
只是，呃，阅读体育比赛
部分或其他东西。
He's in here.
他在这儿。
No, I can't look.
不，我不能看。
>> SpongeBob?
>> 海绵宝宝？
>> Yes?
>> 是吗？
>> Somethin' tells me
>> 有件事告诉我
Mr. Wormsley is actually
a Mrs. Wormsley.
沃姆斯利先生实际上是
沃姆斯利夫人。
>>
>>
Oh, Patrick, it's a miracle.
哦，帕特里克，这是一个奇迹。
>> That...it is.
>> 那个……就是这样。
>> Wait till Gary sees!
>> 等加里看到！
>> Yeah, wait till--
>> 是的，等到——
>> See, Gar?
They're right in here.
>> 看到了吗，加尔？
他们就在这里。
Quiet, now.
They were born less than--
安静吧，现在。
他们出生的时间小于——
>>
>>
>> Looks like they're still
not quite used to each other.
>> 看起来他们还在
彼此都不太习惯。
Well, these things take time.
嗯，这些事情需要时间。
Both: Duck and cover!
两人：闪避并掩护！
>> This town is getting
too rough for me.
>> 这个小镇正在变得
对我来说太粗糙了。
>>
>>
♪ ♪
>> He's chased her away.
>> 他把她赶走了。
Now who will care
for her abandoned litter
现在谁会在乎
为了她遗弃的垃圾
of adorable newborn infants?
可爱的新生婴儿？
>> Well, maybe you can take
care of them.
>> 好吧，也许你可以采取
照顾他们。
>> Oh, no way, Patrick.
>> 噢，不可能，帕特里克。
I've never seen Gary that upset.
我从来没有见过加里那么沮丧。
>> Ga--Who?
>> Nope.
>>嘎--谁？
>> 不。
You and I are just gonna
have to find loving homes
你和我只是要
必须找到有爱的家
for each and every one
of these little guys.
为每一个人
这些小家伙。
Right, Patrick?
对吧，帕特里克？
Patrick?
帕特里克？
Don't worry, little guys,
别担心，小家伙们，
Squidward's a really good
friend of mine,
章鱼哥真的很不错
我的朋友，
and he really likes pets.
而且他真的很喜欢宠物。
>> SpongeBob,
what are you doing here?
>> 海绵宝宝,
你在这里做什么？
Don't you know
that it's 7:00 in the morning?
你不知道吗
现在是早上 7:00？
>> Squidward, I came here
with a special surprise.
>> 章鱼哥，我来了
带着特别的惊喜。
>> Don't you know
that it's 7:00 in the morning?
>> 你不知道吗
现在是早上 7:00？
>> How would you like to have
your very own pet baby worm?
>> 你想要怎样
你自己的宠物小蠕虫？
>> Don't you know that it's--
a what?
>> 你难道不知道那是——
一个什么？
>> Baby worm.
See?
>> 蠕虫宝宝。
看？
Aren't they just adorable
at that age?
它们不是很可爱吗
那个年纪？
So how many did you want?
那么你想要多少个？
>> Yes?
>> 是吗？
Oh, it's you, SpongeBob.
哦，是你，海绵宝宝。
Not that a teacher's
most enthusiastic student
不是老师的
最热情的学生
isn't welcome in her house.
她家里不受欢迎。
>> Good morning, Mrs. Puff.
>> 早上好，普芙女士。
>> It almost was.
>> 几乎就是这样。
>> Would you like a baby worm?
>> 你想要一只小蠕虫吗？
>> A what?
Aaaaaahh!
>> 一个什么？
啊啊啊！
>> I-I'll just come back later,
Mrs. Puff.
>> 我、我稍后再回来，
泡芙女士。
Have a nice day.
祝你今天过得愉快。
>> I hate Mondays.
>> 我讨厌星期一。
>> Don't worry, little worms.
>> 别担心，小虫子。
>> I know a place
we can go to find homes
>> 我知道一个地方
我们可以去找房子
for every single one of you.
为你们每一个人。
Good morning, ma'am.
How are you today?
早上好，女士。
你今天怎么样？
Could I interest you in some--
ma'am?
我可以让你对一些感兴趣吗——
女士？
>>
>>
>> That whistling.
>> 那口哨声。
It's--Larry Lobster!
这是——拉里·龙虾！
Hi, Larry.
What you up to?
嗨，拉里。
你想做什么？
>> Do I know you?
>> 我认识你吗？
>> Probably not.
>> 可能不是。
>> I was just picking up
some dietary supplements
>> 我刚刚接电话
一些膳食补充剂
here at the supermarket.
在超市这里。
I've been working
on my chest and buns.
我一直在工作
在我的胸部和发髻上。
>> So I see.
>> 所以我明白了。
>> Well, catch you later.
>> 好吧，稍后见。
>> Oh, Larry, wait.
>> 哦，拉里，等等。
>> No time now.
>> 现在没时间。
Somewhere there's sand
that needs kicking.
某处有沙子
需要踢。
>> Okay.
>> 好的。
I was just gonna see
if you wanted one of these poor,
我只是想看看
如果你想成为这些穷人中的一员
lonely baby worms.
孤独的小蠕虫。
>> Baby worms?
>> Well yeah, I--
>> 幼虫？
>> 嗯，是的，我——
>> I'll take 'em off your hands.
>> 我会把它们从你手中夺走。
>> Really?
>> Sure, why not?
>> 真的吗？
>> 当然可以，为什么不呢？
That's just
What The Nutritionist Ordered:
那只是
营养师点了什么：
Raw protein.
>> Larry, no!
原料蛋白质。
>> 拉里，不！
>> Oof!
>> 噢！
Dude, nice hustle.
伙计，好热闹。
>>
Err.
>>
错误。
>> Aahh!
>> 啊啊！
Oh, little wormies.
噢，小虫子们。
I'm so glad you're safe.
我很高兴你安全了。
Now, lets go see about finding
you those homes I promised.
现在，让我们看看如何找到
你是我答应过的那些家。
Yello?
>> SpongeBob, it's Mr. Krabs.
耶罗？
>> 海绵宝宝，是蟹老板。
I've been looking all over
for you.
我一直在寻找
为了你。
You're three hours late
for work!
你迟到了三个小时
为了工作！
>> Aaaaaah!
>> 啊啊啊！
>> Hello?
>> 你好？
>>
I'm sorry, Mr. Krabs.
>>
对不起，蟹老板。
I came as quick as I could.
我尽快赶来。
>> SpongeBob, are you sure
you're feeling shipshape?
>> 海绵宝宝，你确定吗
你感觉状态良好吗？
>>
>>
I'm sorry, Mr. Krabs.
对不起，蟹老板。
My pet worm had babies
then got chased away,
我的宠物蠕虫生了孩子
然后就被赶走了
and now I gotta find 'em all
a place to live.
现在我要把他们全部找到
一个居住的地方。
>> Babies?
>> Yeah.
>> 婴儿？
>> 是的。
>> Let me see.
>> 让我看看。
>> Really?
>> Yeah, come on.
>> 真的吗？
>> 是的，来吧。
Let me see 'em.
I like babies.
让我看看他们。
我喜欢婴儿。
>> Well, okay.
>> 好吧，好吧。
>>
Hey, there, little critters.
>>
嘿，那里，小动物们。
Come to--
来——
>> Aw, he likes you.
>> 噢，他喜欢你。
>> Get that disgusting vermin
outta me restaurant, pronto.
>> 消灭那些恶心的害虫
离开我的餐厅，很快。
>>
>>
>> Bleh!
>> 哎呀！
>> Oh, well.
>> 哦，好吧。
At least
I still have you guys.
至少
我还有你们呢。
>>
Hmmm.
>>
嗯。
>> What is it?
>> 这是什么？
>> I'd recognize this goo
anywhere.
>> 我会认出这个粘糊糊的东西
任何地方。
It comes from a baby spotted
glistening meadow worm,
它来自一个被发现的婴儿
闪闪发光的草地蠕虫，
the rarest of its species.
其物种中最稀有的。
>> Dude, those things are worth
a fortune.
>> 伙计，那些东西是值得的
一笔财富。
>> Did you say, "fortune"?
>> 你说的是“财富”吗？
Ka-ching!
嘉庆！
$5.99.
5.99 美元。
That's right,
get 'em while they last.
没错，
趁它们还剩的时候，把它们拿走。
Don't be shy, folks.
别害羞，伙计们。
>> These things are so cute.
>> 这些东西太可爱了。
>> Enjoy your new home,
little guy.
>> 享受你的新家，
小家伙。
>> Isn't he just adorable?
>> 他是不是很可爱？
>> That sure was a great idea
you had, Mr. Krabs.
>> 这确实是个好主意
你有，蟹老板。
>> Well, it's like
they always say
>> 嗯，就像
他们总是说
back in the old country, lad.
回到祖国吧，小伙子。
>> What's that?
>> I don't know.
>> 那是什么？
>> 我不知道。
I've never been
to the old country!
我从来没有去过
到故国去！
♪ ♪
>> Oh, come on, Karen.
Please.
>> 哦，来吧，凯伦。
请。
>> Well, if you must know--
>> 好吧，如果你一定要知道的话——
>> There's nothing wrong
with Chum Bucket fare.
>> 没有什么问题
含 Chum Bucket 票价。
Why, look.
为什么，看。
Here's a fresh batch
of a delicious new chum sauce.
这是一批新鲜的
美味的新密友酱。
It's called
spicy chum surprise.
它被称为
辣密友惊喜。
Uh...
呃...
Delectable.
令人愉快的。
>> Oh, I'm sure it will be
a huge success.
>> 哦，我确信会的
取得了巨大的成功。
>> Sorry, no time
for your senseless chatter.
>> 抱歉，没时间
为了你无意义的喋喋不休。
I've got a customer
to attend to.
我有一个客户
去参加。
>> Okay, so,
>> 好吧，那么，
What about the Krabby Kola?
蟹黄可拉怎么样？
>> We don't serve Krabby Kola.
>> 我们不提供蟹黄可乐。
We carry Bucket Bubbler
and Chum Cherry Blast.
我们携带桶式起泡器
和密友樱桃爆炸。
>> Okay, well then,
can I just make sure
>> 好吧，那么，
我可以确定一下吗
I get those Krabby Fries
with extra Krabby Sauce?
我买了蟹黄薯条
加额外的蟹黄酱？
>>
>>
How many times must I say it?
我必须说多少次？
We don't carry Krabby Fries,
我们不卖蟹黄薯条，
we don't carry Krabby Kola,
我们不携带蟹黄可拉，
we don't carry Krabby Sauce,
我们没有蟹黄酱，
and we don't carry
Krabby Patties!
我们不携带
蟹肉饼！
So if you want
any of those things,
所以如果你想要
任何这些事情，
you're going to have to go
to the Krusty Krab,
你得走了
到蟹堡王，
which is located directly
across the street.
它直接位于
街对面。
>> Thanks for the directions.
>> Any time.
>> 感谢您的指导。
>> 任何时间。
What is wrong with people!
人怎么了！
Honestly, I don't think anyone
in Bikini Bottom would know
老实说，我认为没有人
穿比基尼底就知道
a decent meal if it looked them
right in the eye and said,
如果看起来像一顿美餐
就在眼前说道：
"Hello, I'm a decent meal.
Wonderful to meet you.
“你好，我是一顿饭。
很高兴见到你。
"Please, pay money for me
and then put me in your mouth
“请帮我付钱
然后把我放进你嘴里
"so your old pal Plankton
doesn't lose everything
“所以你的老朋友浮游生物
并没有失去一切
he's spent his entire life
working for!"
他一生都在
为之工作！”
>> Yeah, and if anyone ever did
order one of your meals,
>> 是的，如果有人曾经这样做过
点一份餐食，
it probably would look them
in the eye.
它可能会看起来像他们
在眼睛里。
>> You know, Karen, sometimes
I wonder if you're here
>> 你知道，凯伦，有时
我想知道你是否在这里
to help me run the Chum Bucket
帮助我运行 Chum Bucket
or just to make me feel
like I'm two inches tall.
或者只是为了让我感觉
就像我有两英寸高一样。
Ding!
叮！
>> Maybe in heels.
>> 也许穿高跟鞋。
If it wasn't for me,
如果不是我的话
you probably wouldn't even
remember to blink.
你可能甚至不会
记得眨眼。
>> Oh, come on.
>> 哦，来吧。
When we first met,
you were little more
当我们第一次见面时，
你还差一点
than a jumbled mass
of diodes and wires.
比一团杂乱的东西
二极管和电线。
I made you what you are today,
是我造就了今天的你
literally.
字面上地。
So don't think you couldn't be
replaced in a heartbeat.
所以不要认为你不能
心跳更换。
Ow!
噢！
>> What's the matter?
>> 怎么了？
>> My eye is burning,
and I don't know why!
>> 我的眼睛在燃烧，
我不知道为什么！
>> Blink.
>> 眨眼。
>> Oh, yeah.
Thanks for reminding me.
>> 哦，是的。
谢谢你提醒我。
Now where was I?
现在我在哪里？
>> You were threatening
to replace me.
>> 你在威胁
来代替我。
>> Oh, yeah.
I don't need you!
>> 哦，是的。
我不需要你！
I could make a whole army
of computers
我可以组建一支完整的军队
计算机数量
that might actually help me
steal the formula.
这实际上可能对我有帮助
窃取公式。
>> Oh, puh-leez.
>> 噢，噗噗。
>> I'll show you, woman.
>> 我会告诉你，女人。
Oh, Karen?
哦，凯伦？
>> Now what.
>> 现在做什么。
>> Could you come here
for a moment?
>> 你能过来一下吗
一会儿？
>> What do you want?
>> 你想要什么？
>> Feast your...
Uh...
>> 盛宴您的...
呃...
Screen on this.
屏幕上显示这一点。
♪ ♪
>> That's my replacement?
>> 这是我的替代者吗？
It's a toaster.
这是一个烤面包机。
>> Ha, ha, ha!
>> 哈哈哈哈！
That, my dear,
is a T-119A Compumatic.
那个，亲爱的，
是 T-119A 计算机。
The finest of its kind.
同类中最好的。
>> Good morning, sir.
>> 早上好，先生。
>> Good morning, T-119A!
>> 早上好，T-119A！
They're supposed to do that.
他们应该这样做。
Next, behold
接下来，看
the noxious enterprises
super SP-U31
有害企业
超级SP-U31
liquid-cooled mobile
processing unit.
液冷移动
处理单元。
A mind-staggering combination
of both power and refinement.
令人震惊的组合
力量与精致兼备。
Clunk!
叮当！
>> That'll help you
get the formula.
>> 这会对你有帮助
得到公式。
>> And now, Karen,
the piece  de resistance.
>> 现在，凯伦，
抵抗之作。
Have you ever witnessed
such marvelous machinery?
你是否曾见证过
如此奇妙的机械？
>> It sort of just looks like
an old hair dryer
>> 看起来有点像
一个旧吹风机
taped to the back
of a miniature windmill.
贴在背面
的微型风车。
>> I could see how someone
at your level
>> 我可以看到某人如何
在你的水平
of technical knowledge
would think that, Karen.
技术知识
会这么想，凯伦。
But in actuality
what you are looking at is--
但实际上
你正在看的是——
Oh, right.
哦，对了。
>> I don't recall
you ever having reason
>> 我不记得了
你曾经有过理由
to own a hair dryer, Plankton.
拥有一个吹风机，Plankton。
>> Okay, here we go.
>> 好的，我们开始吧。
Are you gonna make me
get the picture down again?
你要让我
把照片再放下来？
>> What picture?
>> 什么图片？
>> You see?
>> 你看到了吗？
Plenty of reason to be using
a hair dryer.
有充分的理由使用
吹风机。
>> Why are we even talking
about this?
>> 我们为什么要谈论
关于这个？
>> Because you were the one
who said--
>> 因为你就是那个
谁说——
>> What's going on?
>> 这是怎么回事？
>> Dear Neptune!
>> 亲爱的海王星！
Karen, do something.
凯伦，做点什么。
Quick!
快的！
They're tearing
each other apart.
他们在流泪
彼此分开。
Just press a button
or something.
只需按一个按钮
或者什么的。
Not that one!
不是那个！
Aaaaah!
啊啊啊！
>> Well, it's good to see
that strategy didn't fall flat.
>> 嗯，很高兴看到
这一策略并没有失败。
>> You know, Karen,
with you around
>> 你知道，凯伦，
有你在身边
I'm beginning to wonder
how I'm still alive.
我开始想知道
我怎么还活着。
>> Oh, so it's my fault, is it?
>> 哦，所以这是我的错，是吗？
>> That's right!
Now it's all clear.
>> 没错！
现在一切都清楚了。
It's you who've been
holding me back.
原来是你
阻止我。
In fact, if it weren't
for your constant stifling,
事实上，如果不是
为了你不断的窒息，
I'd have the whole world running
for the safety of their mommies!
我会让整个世界运转起来
为了妈妈们的安全！
>> You and your crack team
of robots, huh?
>> 你和你的精英团队
机器人，是吧？
>> Maybe I could iron out
a few bugs.
>>也许我可以解决这个问题
一些错误。
But then you'll see
just how much I need you.
但随后你会看到
我是多么需要你。
Karen?
凯伦？
What's this?
It's words on paper.
这是什么？
这是纸上的话。
It says, "Dear Plankton,
它说：“亲爱的浮游生物，
"I've logged
onto another network.
“我已经登录了
到另一个网络。
"I just can't go into sleep mode
at night
“我就是无法进入睡眠模式
晚上
"knowing that you'll continue
blaming me
“知道你会继续
怪我
"for all of your failures.
“为了你所有的失败。
"Anyway, you're a grown
single-celled organism
“不管怎样，你已经长大了
单细胞生物
"and allowed to make
your own syntax errors.
“并允许使
你自己的语法错误。
Nice knowing you.
--Karen."
很高兴认识你。
——凯伦。”
Ha! Who needs her?
哈!谁需要她？
Not me.
不是我。
I'm going to steal
that Krabby Patty formula
我要去偷
蟹黄派配方
from Mr. Krabs
once and for all.
来自蟹老板
一劳永逸。
And then we'll see
who's made the error.
然后我们就会看到
谁犯了错误。
Ow!
噢！
"p.s.: Don't forget to blink."
“ps：别忘了眨眼。”
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Okay, team.
好的，团队。
Listen up.
听着。
We're on our own now,
我们现在只能靠自己了
so we don't have anything
holding us back.
所以我们什么都没有
阻碍我们。
Now, I know you all look upon me
kindly since I am your creator,
现在，我知道你们都在看着我
善意的，因为我是你的创造者，
but the last thing
the Chum Bucket needs
但最后一件事
密友桶需要
if we are going to be victorious
is a bunch of soft--
如果我们要取得胜利
是一团柔软的——
Uh, software.
呃，软件。
Does everybody understand?
大家都明白了吗？
Ding!
叮！
I said, "Does everybody
understand?"
我说：“大家都
明白吗？”
All right, then.
Let's do this!
好吧，那么。
让我们这样做吧！
T-119A to position.
T-119A 就位。
SP-U31 to position!
SP-U31到位！
Command module to position!
命令模块定位！
Now let's see Krabs stop this.
现在让我们看看蟹老板阻止这一切。
I'll show him.
我会告诉他。
I'll show them all!
我会向他们展示全部！
>> This just in.
>> 这个刚刚进来。
A diabolical albeit haphazardly
thrown together machine
恶魔虽然偶然
拼凑机
is attacking Bikini Bottom
正在攻击比基尼泳裤
and is headed straight
for the Krusty Kra--
并直行
对于 Krusty Kra——
>> Why is the local news
always such rubbish?
>> 为什么是本地新闻
总是这么垃圾？
>> Hey, Squidward, look!
>> 嘿，章鱼哥，看！
I finally figured out a way
to get my mop wet
我终于想出了一个办法
把我的拖把弄湿
without dipping it
in the bucket.
不沾它
在桶里。
>> SpongeBob,
nobody cares about--
>> 海绵宝宝,
没人关心——
>>
>>
Hey!
嘿！
Krabs, I wanna see you.
蟹蟹我想见你
>> Oh, okay, boy.
Get out there.
>> 哦，好吧，孩子。
出去吧。
>> Um, hello.
>> 嗯，你好。
What do you want,
robot thing, sir?
你想要什么，
先生，机器人的事情吗？
Oh, hey, plankton.
What are you doing here?
哦，嘿，浮游生物。
你在这里做什么？
>> I'm here for the secret
formula, you twit.
>> 我来这里是为了秘密
公式，你这个笨蛋。
I want you to go in there
and tell Krabs
我要你进去
并告诉蟹老板
that if he doesn't turn over
the formula to me,
如果他不翻身
给我的公式，
he will be subjected
to utter annihilation at my--
他将受到
彻底消灭我的——
Are you getting this?
你明白了吗？
>> Mm-hmm.
>> 嗯嗯。
>> Ugh! Moron.
>> 呃！白痴。
Okay, I'll make it simple.
好吧，我会简单点的。
Krabs give me secret formula,
螃蟹给我秘方，
or I bring big boom-boom
to Krusty Krab.
或者我带来巨大的繁荣
到蟹堡王。
Got it?
知道了？
>> Krabs give me
secret formula, or--
>> 螃蟹给我
秘密配方，或者——
What was that other thing?
那另一件事是什么？
>> Argh, forget it!
>> 唉，算了！
Bring on the boom-boom!
带来繁荣繁荣！
>> Battle stations, men!
Here he comes!
>> 战斗站，伙计们！
他来了！
>> We're all doomed!
We're all doomed!
>> 我们都注定了！
我们都注定了！
We're all doomed!
Doomed, doomed,
doomed, doomed, doomed!
注定了，注定了，
注定了，注定了，注定了！
We're all doomed!
我们都注定了！
>> Later.
>> 稍后。
>>
>>
Hey, what gives?
嘿，什么给？
>>
>>
>> Bwah-hoo-hoo!
>> 哇呼呼！
>>
>>
Oh, curse you, cruel fate!
哦，诅咒你，残酷的命运！
Once again,
you've left me covered
再一次，
你让我掩护
in the sticky goo
of my own folly.
在粘稠的粘液中
我自己的愚蠢行为。
Only this time...
I'm all alone.
只是这一次...
我孤身一人。
>>
>>
Karen!
凯伦！
You've come back to me.
你已经回到我身边了。
>> Actually, I just came
to get my keyboard.
>> 其实我刚来
拿到我的键盘。
>> Oh, I knew
you couldn't stay away.
>>哦，我知道
你不能离开。
I knew it.
我就知道。
>>
Right.
>>
对。
Let Me Guess:
Another failure?
让我猜猜：
又一次失败？
>> What're ya gonna do?
Machines these days, right?
>> 你要做什么？
现在的机器，对吧？
Uh, listen, sweetie,
呃，听着，亲爱的，
I'm sorry about what I said.
我对我所说的话感到抱歉。
The truth is, I could never
replace you, honey bunch.
事实是，我永远无法
取代你，亲爱的。
Let's go home, huh?
我们回家吧，嗯？
>>
okay.
>>
好的。
>> Hey, I could whip us up
a little dinner.
>> 嘿，我可以鞭策我们
一点晚餐。
What do you say?
你怎么说？
>> You want me
to leave you again?
>> 你想要我
又要离开你了吗？
>> Or we could go out.
That'd be fun too.
>> 或者我们可以出去。
那也很有趣。
Captioning by captionmax
www.captionmax.com
字幕由captionmax提供
♪ ♪